

NODE JS DEVELOPER

0781468561

mucyochristian2@gmail.com LinkedIn: mucyo-c-a90064128

## **ABOUTME**

I'm a self taught motivated Node JS developer, with an experience of 2 years. Quality product, and keeping my stakeholder's updated is always my priority. I am fully determined in my every action, backed by my integrity of learning fast and quick delivery.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Mar 2021 - Present

Contractor - Kigalimart

Developing a mobile app that will work as broker, for all ecommerces in Rwanda, with delivery service integrated.

# Jul 2020 - Present

Freelancer

- Website Design
- Web and Mobile App Development

# Feb 2020 - Jul 2020

Apprentice in Andela

- I got knowledge in soft skills and team play.
- Development of Accomodation booking system.
- Analysis of user requirements, design system and mockup for project.
- · Agile methodology practice.
- CI Testing and API documenting.

# May 2018 - Nov 2018

Intern in TRES Ltd

- Development of Property Listing Management System.
- Introduced to version control (Git)

## Jan 2018 - Nov 2019

Trainee in software development

- Learned Web design.
- Learned Web application Development
- Learned Database Development (Mysql)
- Learned Designing system diagram (Use Case, Workflow)

# **EDUCATION**

2019 Software Develoment

SOS Technical High School

2023 ≥ Software Engineering

UNILAK

C1

# LANGUAGE SKILLS

Kinyarwanda C2

**English** 

French Α1

## **COMPUTER SKILLS**

Full Stack Developer

HTML & (CSS, SASS)

**JavaScript** 

ReactJS & ReactNative

NodeJS & Express

Version Control (Git)

Agile Methodology

